Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Jesse Ely Wills Papers
1915-1977
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0001
2.52 linear_feet
Jesse Ely Wills, 1899-1977, a Nashville native, was a member of the group of poets who met in Nashville in the early 1920's to write and publish the influential literary magazine The Fugitive. He was an officer and executive of the National Life and Accident Insurance Company during his business career and was active in Vanderbilt University affairs as a member of the Board of Trust and chairman of the Board of the Joint University Libraries.
This collection contains literary correspondence, poems, and manuscripts of poet and businessman Jesse Ely Wills.
- Correspondence - Outgoing, 1952-1977 (Box 1, Folder 1-6)
  Arranged chronologically. 484 letters, the bulk of which consists of typed carbons.
- Correspondence - Incoming, 1951-1976 (Box 1, Folder 7-14)
  492 letters, most typed, many holograph. Six postcards, three Christmas cards. Two telegrams. Arranged alphabetically according to sender.
- Miscellaneous essays and reviews by Jesse E. Wills (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Review. The Dream Songs by John Berryman. Holograph and typed carbon (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Review. The Eguilibrist: A Study of John Crowe Ransom's Poems~ 1916-1963 by Robert Buffington. typed carbon (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Memoirs of Far Hills." typed carbon (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "For Coffee House." photocopy (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - "Professor C.B. Wallace and Wallace School .. " typed carbon (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Newspaper clippings (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Donald Davidson (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 25 April 1968, Obituary Notice (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 26 April 1968, Nashville Banner: "Davidson Rites Slated; Famed Poet." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 26 April 1968, Nashville Tennessean: "Prof. Davidson, 'Fugitive' Poet Dies at 72." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 26 April 1968, Nashville Banner: "Donald Davidson," editorial (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 27 April 1968, Nashville Tennessean: "Mr. Davidson was Rare Figure," editorial (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 28 April 1968, Nashville Tennessean: "Gentle and Dear Friend" by Floy Beatty (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 21 May 1968, National Review: "Donald Davidson, RIP." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 24 July 1968, Nashville Banner: If JUL Acquires Papers of 'Fugitive' Dr. Davidson .. " (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - John Crowe Ransom (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 6 July 1967, Nashville Tennessean: "Ransom Picked To Receive $10,000 Prize." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 31 December 1967, Nashville Tennessean: "Ransom Study Most Thorough." Reviewed by Jesse Wills (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 25 April 1969, Nashville Banner: "Writers Conference at Cumberland May 2." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 26 April 1968, Nashville Tennessean: "Fugitive To Be Feted on 80th." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 29 April 1968, Nashville Banner: "J.C. Ransom, 'Fugitive' To Be Honored." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 14 May 1968, Vanderbilt Hustler: "Fugitive John Crowe Ransom Wins Emerson-Thoreau Medal." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 4 July 1974, Tennessean: "Ransom, Fugitive Poet, Dies." (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Alec B. Stevenson (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 27 May 1969, Obituary (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 27 May 1969, Nashville Banner: "Alec B. Stevenson Dies, Rites at 3 Wednesday." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 28 May 1969, Nashville Tennessean: "Alec Stevenson Services Today." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 28 May 1969, Nashville Banner: "Alec B. Stevenson," editorial (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 30 May 1969, Nashville Tennessean: "Mr. Stevenson Will Be Missed .. " (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Eldon Stevenson, Jr. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 4 March 1970, Nashville Banner: "VU Names Science Center In Honor of Stevenson." (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Allen Tate (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 7 August 1966, Nashville Tennessean: "Allen Tate Marries Miss Heinz." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 12 January 1969, "Churches To Present U.S. Leaders" by Charles Thompson (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1 June 1969, Nashville Tennessean: "Compleat Allen Tate," reviewed by M. Thomas Inge (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 5 October 1975, Nashville Tennessean: "Allen Tate's Latest Traces His Development" by Sara Morrow (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 28 December 1975, Nashville Tennessean: "Sewanee's Tate Recipient of NY Literary Award." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 20 May 1976, Nashville Banner: "Allen Tate Awarded National Medal." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - n.d., Robert Penn Warren "Allen Tate To Receive Merrill Prize." (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Robert Penn Warren (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 11 April, Nashville Banner: "Three Major Writers, Critics To Speak at VU." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 19 April 1968, Nashville Banner: "Poetry Symposium Draws Heavy Crowd at Vanderbilt," by Howell Pearre (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 19 April 1968, Nashville Tennessean: "'Fugitive' Cites Chaos in Words at VU Talk" by Rhodes Johnston. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 31 July 1970, Women's Wear Daily: "Tall, Graceful Eleanor Clark is a Natural," by Brenda Badolato. (Eleanor Clark is Mrs. Robert Penn Warren.) (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 10 November 1974, The Tennessean: "Collected Poems Span Six Years." Review of 'Or Else: Poem/Poems 1968-1974.' Reviewed by Frances Neel Cheney (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - n.d. "Robert Penn Warren Wins Bollingen Prize In Poetry." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - n.d. "Warren's Poetry Honored." (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Jesse Ely Wills (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 11 November 1954, Nashville Banner: "Phi Beta Kappa Selection Honors Four VU Alumni." (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 17 January 1971, Nashville Tennessean: "Poet in the Money Making Businessu by Louise Davis" (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 5 November 1971, Nashville Banner: "VU Trustees Elect Two New Life Members" (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - William R. Wills (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Obituary Notice (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Others (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 23 March 1960, Nashville Tennessean: "VU Divinity School Alumni Ask Lawson Reinstatement" by Edmund Willingham (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 21 April 1968, Nashville Tennessean: "'Fugitives' Reaffirm Need for Man's Individuality" (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 23 January 1974, The Tennessean: "Richard Wilbur Slated at Vanderbilt Tonight" (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Photographs (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sculptured bust of Robert Penn Warren by Joan Fitzgerald, four views (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Sculptured bust of Ezra Pound by Joan Fitzgerald (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Essays, statements by others (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Davidson, Donald. Introduction to Peter Smith reprint of The.Fugitive. typed carbon (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Kaser, David. A Fugitive Collection in the Joint University Libraries. typed (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Moore, Merrill. On the First Presbyterian Church in Nashville, Tennessee. photocopy, negative (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Taylor, Peter with William Breit, Leland Yeager. James Muir Waller, 1900-1971. electrostatic copy (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Van Antwerp, Chiles. The Old Oak Club ,mimeograph copy (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Reprints, material by others (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Aden, John M. "Student Revolt and the Humanities: A Non-Negotiable Dissent." Southern Humanities Review, Vol. 5, Spring 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Jones, David Howell. Announcement of Donald Davidson: An Essay and a Bibliography (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Tate, Allen. "A Lost Traveller's Dream." Michigan Quarterly Review, Autumn 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Warren, Robert Penn. "Who is Relevant?U Yale Alumni Magazine, February 1971 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Miscellaneous (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
  - American Committee for Cultural Freedom. Statement (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Mizener Papers. Bill of Sale (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Maxey Jarman Kitchen Cabinet. Two Membership cards (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Items showing his relationship with Allen Tate (Box 1, Folder 20-21)
- Old Oak and Coffee House Papers, including drafts and later supplements to the papers, 1930-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - The Age We Live In - Old Oak Club, 1937
  - America and the Crisis - Old Oak Club, 1941
  - The Battle of Midway - Old Oak Club, 1950
  - A Business Man Looks at Labor Unions - Old Oak Club, 1947
  - Catechism on Present and Future - Old Oak Club, 1936
  - Changes on the Weather - Coffee House, 1957
  - Changes on the Weather - Old Oak Club, 1958
  - Impressions of a Traveler Concerning Williamsburg, Virginia - Old Oak Club, 1937
  - In the Matter of John Masefield - Old Oak Club, Coffee House, 1969
  - The Problems of Air Power - Old Oak Club, 1943
  - Prose and Poetry - Old Oak Club, Coffee House, 1961
  - The Revolutions Around Us - Old Oak Club, 1965
  - A Southern Christian Considers Race - Old Oak Club, 1952
- Juvenilia, circa 1915-1920 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Fugitive verse, 1922-1925 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Agriochaerus". 1 typescript, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Arlington National Cemetary". 1 typescript, holograph note (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Aunt Minnie I, II, III". 1 typescript (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Automobile Ride". 1 typescript, 4 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Black Sheep". 1 typescript 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Changes". 1 typescript, holograph revisions (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Consider the Heavens". 2 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Crystal Gazer". 2 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "The Depths". 1 typescript (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Dream". 2 holograph, 2 typescript (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Dust". 1 typescript, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Eden". 2 typescript with holograph revisions, 3 carbons, 1 holograph note (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "False Dawn". 1 typescript, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Fear I, II". 1 typescript entitled "Egomania", 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Felix Adair". 2 typescript, 4 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "From a Window". 2 holograph, 1 typescript (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "A Fundamentalist". 1 typescript, 4 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Healing". 1 typescript, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "The Hills Remember". 1 typescript, 2 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Lausanne". 1 typescript (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Lightning's Blink". 1 typescript, 2 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Night Windows". 2 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Parable". 3 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Premonition", 1 typescript, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Primavera", 1 typescript, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "The Proposal". 1 typescript with notes in another hand, 3 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Red Even". 3 holograph, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Riddle". 1 holograph, 1 typescript, 2 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Snow Prayers I, II, III". 1 typescript, 3 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "The Survivors". 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Three Rabbits". 1 typescript (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "To a Tired Clerk". 2 carbons (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "To the Bugle Not Blown". 1 holograph (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - "Trinity". 1 typescript, 1 carbon (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - Untltled poem: "I Tossed an Arm Out...". 1 typescript with holograph (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
  - revision, 1 typescript, 2 carbons. Fragments: 8 pages holograph (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
- Economic Discussion Group, 1931-1933 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Early and Late - Rough drafts, intermediate and final drafts, typescript (printer's copy), page proofs, business correspondence, congratulatory correspondence, reviews (Box 3, Folder 1-6)
- Notes, remarks on poetry readings (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Introduction of Jesse E. Wills on occasion of a poetry reading by Frances Neel Cheney, 12 November, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Tapes of poetry reading by Jesse E. Wills, 12 November, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Tapes of poetry reading by Jesse E. Wills, 14 November, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Script of WPLN broadcast with Lin Folk, 8 April, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Meditations on the American Indian - Drafts, typescript (printer's copy), page proofs, published copy in paper cover (Box 3, Folder 10-12)
- Conversation Piece - Notes and early drafts, intermediate and final drafts, page proofs, analytical letter from Donald Davidson (Box 4, Folder 1-5)
- Nashville and Other Poems - Notes and early drafts, intermediate and final drafts, typescript (printer's copy), page proofs (Box 4, Folder 6-11)
- Selected Poems - Early drafts, page proofs, correspondence reviews (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
- A Diversity of Interests - Draft copies, typescript, printer's copy, correspondence, essays not included in the publication, published copy in paper covers (Box 5, Folder 4-9)
- Occasional verse (Box 5, Folder 10)
- "First Lady" - Several drafts of a contemplated poem on Mrs. John F. Kennedy, Not completed (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Vanderbilt affiliations - Correspondence and reports concerning committee work (Box 6, Folder 1-19)
  - Academic Programs Committee (Box 6, Folder 1-3)
  - Ad hoc Committee on Composition of Undergraduate Student Body (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Committee for Fort Flowers Wing Dedication (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Naming Buildings (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Committee on Strengthening Athletics (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Educational Programs Committee (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Ethiopian Microfilming Project (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Fraternity Study Committee (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Graduate School of Management (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - JUL Building Fund (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - JUL Fugitive Room (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Lawson Case (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Long-Range Financial Planning Committee (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Ponzine, Raymond E. and Huber, Donald C. - Poetry Reading at Vanderbilt (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Resolutions on the death of Vanderbilt Associates (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Telecast of Basketball Games (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - W.R. Wills Center for Psychiatric Treatment and Research (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Obituaries and Tributes (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Outgoing Correspondence Index
  - Merrill Moore, 26 August, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Coley Harwell, 26 August, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - George Mayfield, 8 November, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Red" (Robert Penn Warren), 15 June, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - William F. Orr, 31 July, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - William Batts, 5 September, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, 30 April, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, 9 June, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Bill" (William Yandell Elliott), 9 June, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - "Lib" (Mrs. R.D. Crabtree), 17 December, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 7 January, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Ann Leslie Moore, 7 April, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, 10 April, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Caroline Gordon, 29 April, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ann Leslie Moore, 18 May, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Eldon Stevenson, Jr., (unsigned), 10 March, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Sally (Mrs. Lewis Barr Flinn, Jr.), 22 April, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Harvey Branscomb, 2 June, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Howard Hall, 29 December, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Guy Owen, 22 February, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Guy Owen, 26 December, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Guy Owen, 3 January, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, 9 April, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, 15 May, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - James M. Waller, 23 May, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Brainard Cheney, 10 September, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Lytle, 7 November, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 9 January, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Lawrence S. Thompson, 26 March, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Matt Wigginton, 24 December, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Horace Hill, 24 May, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Horace Hill, 11 June, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Fort Flowers, 14 June, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Alexander Heard, 14 June, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Alexander Heard, 14 June, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Harold Vanderbilt, 1 July, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Reber Boult, 3 August, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 12 October, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Frances Neel Cheney (Mrs. Brainard), 18 October, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jud Collins, 4 January, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - John H. Dewitt, Jr., 4 January, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - David Howell Jones, 4 February, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen Tate, 9 February, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Donald Davidson, 10 February, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen Tate, 23 February, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - J. Lasley Dameron, 25 February, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - David Kaser, 18 March, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Alec Stevenson, 18 March, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Peter J. Tharp, 29 April, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen Tate, 22 August, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Edith H. Wolfe, 4 October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alec Stevenson, 24 October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Donald Davidson, 25 October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - John Crowe Ransom, 25 October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen Tate, 25 October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 25 October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Donald Davidson, 30 October, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Margaret Williams, 2 November, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen Tate, 14 November, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 15 November, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Henry E. Niles, 6 December, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ridley Wills, 5 April, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 18 April, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 18 April, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Steve (Alec B. Stevenson), 24 April, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Robert Penn Warren, Alec B. Stevenson, 9 May, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Donald Davidson, 18 May, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Edwin F. Hunt, 22 May, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, Rob Roy Purdy, 25 May, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 25 July, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Allen Tate, 4 August, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Louis Farrell, Jr., 11 October, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - James K. Flack, 12 October, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Margaret Williams, 26 October, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - James A. Simpson, William Waller, Sr., 1 November, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - James K. Flack, 15 November, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Robert L. Garner, 16 November, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Floy Beaty, 18 December, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth and John K. Maddin, 12 January, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - James K. Flack, Andrew Lytle, 24 January, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 25 January, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 13 February, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Greg Tucker, 5 March, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 18 March, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 8 April, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Robert Penn Warren, Matthew B. Wills, 22 April, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - William C. Pratt, 24 April, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, Andrew Lytle, 25 April, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - James M. Waller, 7 May, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - William C. Pratt, Robert Penn Warren, 20 May, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 27 May, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - David Käser, 28 May, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ann Leslie Moore, 10 June, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Edwin S. Gardner, 12 June, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 2 July, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore, 8 July, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Roy B. Basler, 8 July, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Ann Leslie Moore, 11 July, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 15 July, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 18 July, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Allen Tate, Andrew Lytle, 1 August, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 5 August, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Randolph Harrison, 6 August, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ernest Choate, 3 September, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - May (Mrs. David F, Hall), 11 September, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, Pete (Robert L. Naylor), 16 September, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 18 September, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 23 September, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, 30 September, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Frank Grisham, 9 October, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Thomas D. Young, 20 November, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Heard, 5 December, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - John Sloan, 5 December, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, George Cate, Jr., Mrs. Albert Werthan, John Bransford, 17 December, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, 19 December, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Edwin S. Gardner, 30 December, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Heard, Matt S. Wigginton, George Cate, Jr., Mrs. Albert Werthan, John Bransford, Alec B, Stevenson, 2 January, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Allen Tate, Alec B. Stevenson, 9 January, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - T. Daniel Young, 13 January, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 20 January, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 3 February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, Thomas D. Young, 4 February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 5 February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, 5 February, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - William S. Vaughn, 6 February, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Frank Grisham, 6 February, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Edwin S. Gardner, 10 February, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Mrs. Merrill Moore, 10 February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, Allen Tate, 11 February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 27 February, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, Mrs. Merrill Moore, 4 March, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 12 March, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Frank P. Grisham, 17 March, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 18 March, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Donald Davidson, Rob Roy Purdy, 19 March, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, William Yandell Elliott, Robert Penn Warren, 31 March, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Madison S. Wigginton, Frank P. Grisham, 31 March, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - James A. Simpson, William H. Vanderbilt, 10 April, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, 10 April, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Thomas F. Heffernan, 14 April, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - William Waller, 15 April, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Betsy Wilson, 21 April, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Geddes Douglas, Sr., 20 April, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - . Allen Tate, 29 April, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alec B. Stevenson, 29 April, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - William Yandell Elliott, 19 May, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, Robert Penn Warren, 19 May, 1969
  - Carolyn and William A. McDonnell, 20 May, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Matt S. Wigginton, 26 May, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Robert A. McGaw, 27 May, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 27 May, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Edwin S. Gardner, William Yandell Elliott, 28 May, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Orrin W. Jones, 29 May, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Charles S. Ragland, 2 June, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Woodrow W. Wasson, 3 June, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Charles S. Ragland, James A. Simpson, Nicholas Hobbs, 12 June, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alexander Heard, 16 June, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 16 June, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - William Yandell Elliott, 17 June, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Robert Penn Warren, 18 June, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Charles S. Ragland, 18 June, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Allen Tate, William Yandell Elliott, 30 June, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 2 July, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Andrew Lytle, 7 July, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Manning, 8 July, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - William Yandell Elliott, 13 August, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Frank Baker, 28 August, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Allen Tate, 8 September, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Members of the Trustee Committee on Academic Programs of Vanderbilt University, 10 September, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Wills, 15 September, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rob Roy Purdy, 16 September, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Thomas Daniel Young, 16 September, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ann Leslie Moore, Robert Penn Warren, 17 September, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Allen Tate, 24 September, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)